narutowire.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy - NWAnime

**Please use 'Report Broken Link' tab in video page or 'Technical Difficulties' message board in forum to report broken links!!**

Privacy Policy 

  The use of this version of the "NWAnime.tv" website and/or NWAnime.tv software and any other related software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers provided by "NWAnime.tv" are subject to the hereunder provisions of this Privacy Policy.: 

General 

  "NWAnime.tv" takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information, which we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. 

  BY USING OR ACCESSING ANY NWAnime.tv WEBSITE OR DOWNLOADING AND USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. NWAnime.com MAY AMEND THIS POLICY FROM TIME TO TIME. 

  If you are under the age of 13, you are not eligible to use the Service, and we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. 

Collection of Information 

**Personal Information:** Use of certain features of the Service may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nick name (or other user ID) and a password. 

**Non personally identifiable Information:** NWAnime.tv may also collect or receive additional non personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the NWAnime.tv Service or website(s), and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on NWAnime.tv's Service and/or website(s). 

  "NWAnime.tv" may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non personally identifiable technical information, when the NWAnime.tv website(s) and pages are visited or when the NWAnime.tv Service is used. 

**How is the information being used?** The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you by NWAnime.tv, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you ; to fulfill your requests for Services, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Service and/or website(s), offerings and advertisements presented on NWAnime.com Service, email communication, website(s) and pages; and to help offer you other Services, programs, or services that may be of interest. 

_Any personally identifiable information of yours_ will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. NWAnime.tv may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of NWAnime.tv users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you. 

_Notwithstanding the foregoing_ , your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures. 

**Cookies:   ** "NWAnime.tv" may use cookies or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Service and/or of NWAnime.tv's website, including to operate and improve offerings through the Service and/or website; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Service, and/or website; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you. 

  Additionally, "NWAnime.com" or its advertisers may use other companies, known as third party ad servers to help present advertisements online in connection with the Service, and/or web sites. These third party ad servers may use cookies or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies, not NWAnime.com's. 

  "NWAnime.tv" does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Services and/or web sites may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements** Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Special Note for Parents 

  "NWAnime.tv"'s Service and website are not intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen (13) are not permitted to register with NWAnime.com's Service and websites. 

Modification and Deletion of Personally Identifiable Information (Opt-Out) 

  In order to delete the personally identifiable information you submitted, notify us, to the following email address: support[at]nwanime.com that you wish to delete your personally identifiable information or any part thereof contained at our databases. 

Modification 

  If you wish to modify or update your personally identifiable information, use the web-site or application interface. If you need help, please contact us at the following email address: support@nwanime.com. Please note that deletion of your personally identifiable information from NWAnime.tv's database will not prevent NWAnime.tv from using gathered anonymous information. 

**Third Parties' Practices**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**Sharing or Usage**  
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone for their promotional use without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information, and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.
